https://www.uagroup.co.uk/privacy-policy

Headquarters
Stirling Agricultural Centre,
Menu
HomeAbout UsCompany HistoryExecutive TeamStirling Bull SalesAuction SalesSales ReportsStirlingHuntlyLairgDalmallyObanKelsoIslayTireeLochboisdalePrivate SalesDispersalsPropertyNews & MediaLatest NewsPress ReleasesPublicationsContactLocationsSales TeamEnquiries
Live Webcam
Privacy Policy
Privacy & Cookies
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.
What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:
information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit, pages viewed and activity on each page);
information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters including contact details.
any other information that you choose to send to us via forms, email and other methods.
Using your personal data
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information to:
improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
send to you our newsletter(s) and other marketing communications relating to our business
Cookies
A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. We use both "session" cookies and "persistent" cookies on our websites. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and to monitor user behaviour for statistical and marketing purposes. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit. Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.
Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.
You can learn more about cookies and how to reject cookies using different types of browser by visiting http://www.allaboutcookies.or
Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. View Google's privacy policy also for more on cookies and Google Analytics.
Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.
Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
Headquarters
Stirling Agricultural Centre
Stirling FK9 4RN
01786 473055
info@uagroup.co.uk
> Contacts & Locations
© Copyright 2018, United Auctions
United Auctions is a trading name of UA Livestock Limited
Registered in Scotland number SC303729
Site by Vizibility
Terms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicySitemap
Cookies
We use cookies on our website to distinguish you from other users which helps provide a good experience and also allows us to improve our website. To learn more about cookies, how we use them on our website and how to change your cookie settings, please view our Privacy Policy.
Ok
